so let's discuss the solution for our
speed-up averaging quiz we only have the
speed ups for the two applications and
we have said previously that an
arithmetic average of speed ups does not
make sense you should not use arithmetic
averaging for speed ups because there
are ratios of execution times so the
only thing that does make sense to use
on speed ups in this case is a geometric
mean thus the speed up we need is a 2
times 8 and then there are 2 values so
we take the second root of that and we
get a number 4 so the correct answer
here is the speed up is 4 again doing
something like 2 plus 8 over 2 is not
correct here because these are ratios
you should not use the normal arithmetic
mean for that